{
  "questions": [
    {
      "questionText": "12-(4+3)?",
      "answers": [ "10", "15", "2", "3", "24", "5" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 5
    },
    {
      "questionText": "(45 - 5) / 8 + 2?",
      "answers": [ "16", "9", "7", "77", "24", "90" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "questionText": "(2+3)^2?",
      "answers": [ "25", "7", "50", "88", "90", "45" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "questionText": "3 + 4 * 5?",
      "answers": [ "89", "23", "76", "42", "11", "37" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "questionText": "5 + 3 * 4 - 6?",
      "answers": [ "22", "33", "44", "67", "11", "55" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 4
    },
    {
      "questionText": "20 - 8 / 2?",
      "answers": [ "16", "99", "18", "27", "22", "35" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "questionText": "9 / (2 + 1) * 8?",
      "answers": [ "100", "12", "24", "33", "54", "22" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "questionText": " 6 + 4 / 2 + 3^2?",
      "answers": [ "19", "25", "67", "21", "22", "17" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 5
    },
    {
      "questionText": "4 + 2 * 3^2?",
      "answers": [ "23", "22", "24", "61", "34", "99" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "questionText": " 50 - 4 * 3^2?",
      "answers": [ "78", "66", "23", "14", "18", "22" ],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 3
    }
  ]
}
